It didn't work because
Kentucky is different.
Kentucky is different from California
and New York. The patients are different...
...from Brazil and London. The model was built
on 400 million patients across the world.
What we needed was a model built
on Kentucky patients...
...with Kentucky data,
with Kentucky problems.
The Cabinet for Health and Family Services
has a state-university partnership...
...where you can propose getting access
to state data - super valuable data.
Now it's up to us to figure out how to use
that data to make healthcare better.
The final one is essentially
cancer screening.
Can we get ahold of Medicaid claims data
and identify patients eligible for screening...
...whether it's colon cancer, lung cancer,
or cervical cancer...
...find those patients, and deploy
similar software to reach out to them?
We think we can design an AI agent
that walks you through the process...
...and schedules your appointment
at the same time...
...so you don't have to take the onus
on yourself of calling your doctor...
...and trying to get a colonoscopy.
We can do it automatically...
...bring you in, and make sure we are caring
for the people of Kentucky.
We don't want California.
We don't want New York.
We want Kentucky's data
so we can better impact Kentuckians.
We want this to be
a dynamic conversation...
...about what we can do to streamline
and provide better access to data...
...more quickly. Whatever we need to do
on our side...
...we want to be a good partner.